In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to learn how to pronounce the AW as in LAW vowel.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音AW，如同LAW中的元音。
This vowel sound, when pure, is quite similar to the AH as in FATHER vowel.
这个元音音素，当它是纯音时，与FATHER中的AH元音非常相似。
In some areas of the United States, we don't even make this sound, we always use the AH as in FATHER sound instead.
在美国的一些地区，我们甚至不发这个音，我们总是用FATHER中的AH音代替。
Also, when this vowel is followed by the R consonant, it changes.
此外，当这个元音后面跟着R辅音时，它会发生变化。
We'll go over that.
我们将对此进行讲解。
First, let's study the mouth position.
首先，让我们研究一下口腔位置。
To make this vowel, the jaw drops and the tongue shifts back.
要发这个元音，下巴下垂，舌头向后移动。
The tip of the tongue doesn't touch anything.
舌尖不接触任何东西。
The lips flare a bit.
嘴唇稍微张开。
AW.
AW。
One technique that might help you make this sound is to think of the cheeks coming in and shifting forward just a little bit.
一种可能帮助你发出这个音的技巧是想象脸颊稍微向内并向前移动一点。
AW.
AW。
This is a way to make it different from the AW as in FATHER vowel, where the lips and cheeks are totally relaxed.
这是一种使其与FATHER中的AW元音不同的方法，在FATHER中，嘴唇和脸颊是完全放松的。
AW.
AW。
Let's watch up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观看。
The jaw drops, the lips flare out a little bit, and the tongue pulls back.
下巴下垂，嘴唇稍微张开，舌头向后拉。
Let's compare with the AW as in FATHER vowel on top.
让我们将其与FATHER中的AW元音进行比较。
In AW, the lips are relaxed.
在AW中，嘴唇是放松的。
In AW, the lips flare.
在AW中，嘴唇张开。
Also, notice how the tongue pulls back in the AW vowel.
还要注意舌头在AW元音中如何向后拉。
In a stressed syllable, this vowel has the up-down shape of stress.
在重读音节中，这个元音有上下的重音形状。
AW.
AW。
For example, in the word SAW.
例如，在单词SAW中。
Jaw drops, lips flare, tongue shifts back.
下巴下垂，嘴唇张开，舌头向后移动。
In an unstressed syllable, the voice will be lower in pitch.
在非重读音节中，声音的音调会更低。
Quieter and flatter.
更安静和平坦。
Unstressed syllables won't be as long.
非重读音节不会那么长。
AW, AW.
AW, AW。
The voice is unstressed in the word ON.
在单词ON中，声音是非重读的。
A function word.
一个功能词。
ON.
ON。
Function words are unstressed.
功能词是非重读的。
AW, AW.
AW, AW。
Note, this word can also be pronounced with the AW as in FATHER vowel.
注意，这个词也可以用FATHER中的AW元音发音。
The vowel here is extremely quick, since it's in an unstressed syllable.
由于它在非重读音节中，这里的元音非常快。
The tongue tip isn't quite forward.
舌尖不完全向前。
The tongue is in position just an instant before the tongue flips up to make the N.
舌头在翻上去发N音之前只在一个瞬间处于位置。
Let's compare the stressed AW in SAW on top with the unstressed AW in ON on the bottom.
让我们将SAW中的重读AW与ON中的非重读AW进行比较。
You can see the jaw drops less, the lips are more relaxed, and the tongue doesn't shift back as much.
你可以看到下巴下垂得更少，嘴唇更放松，舌头没有向后移动那么多。
Unstressed syllables are shorter than stressed syllables, so often the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong doesn't take the full mouth position of the stressed version.
非重读音节比重读音节短，所以通常非重读版本的元音或双元音不会采取重读版本的完整口腔位置。
This vowel can be affected by following consonants.
这个元音可能会受到后续辅音的影响。
When the AW vowel is followed by the R consonant, the sound does change.
当AW元音后面跟着R辅音时，声音确实会改变。
The lips flare more, and the tongue pulls back more, and up a little bit.
嘴唇张开更多，舌头向后拉更多，并稍微向上。
This is because we blend the position for the R with the position for the AW, when the R follows the AW.
这是因为当R跟在AW后面时，我们将R的位置与AW的位置混合。
Instead of AW, the sound is AW, coo-r, aw, aw.
而不是AW，声音是AW，coo-r, aw, aw。
Let's look at another word.
让我们看看另一个单词。
Soar, aw, aw.
Soar, aw, aw。
Let's compare the pure AW with the AW followed by R in the word QUARTER on the bottom.
让我们将纯AW与在单词QUARTER中跟着R的AW进行比较。
You can see for the AW followed by R, the lips round more, and the jaw drops less.
你可以看到对于跟着R的AW，嘴唇更圆，下巴下垂更少。
Because of the lips, it's hard to see the tongue, but it pulls back and up more than in a pure AW vowel above.
由于嘴唇，很难看到舌头，但它比上面的纯AW元音向后和向上拉得更多。
Pure stressed AW.
纯重读AW。
Saw, aw.
Saw, aw。
Pure unstressed AW.
纯非重读AW。
Un, aw.
Un, aw。
AW, aw.
AW, aw。
AW modified by R.
被R修饰的AW。
Coar, aw, aw.
Coar, aw, aw。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Boss, aw, boss.
Boss, aw, boss。
Long, aw, long.
Long, aw, long。
Aw, aw.
Aw, aw。
Run off.
Run off。
Lifelong.
Lifelong。
Aw, lifelong.
Aw, lifelong。
Login.
Login。
AW, login.
AW, login。
Wrong.
Wrong。
AW, wrong.
AW, wrong。
Daughter.
Daughter。
Aw, daughter.
Aw, daughter。